Button, Daniel Evan; Papers apap231
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Communication, 1965-1970; Undated; 6; 2.6 cubic ft.
  - H.R. 17 Medals of Honor to astronauts, 1969 (Box 1 (6-Communication), Folder 164)
  - H.R. 165 Irish immigration, 1967-1969 (Box 1 (6-Communication), Folder 165)
  - H.R. 220 to equalize retired pay of the uniformed services, 1969 (Box 1 (6-Communication), Folder 166)
  - H.R. 339 to create a catalog of Federal Assistance Programs, 1969 (Box 1 (6-Communication), Folder 167)
  - H.R. 6736 Public Television Act, 1967; Undated (Box 1 (6-Communication), Folder 168)
  - H.R. 7819, Elementary and Secondary Education Act of 1967 (Box 1 (6-Communication), Folder 169)
  - H.R. 13000, 1969 (Box 1 (6-Communication), Folder 170)
  - Human Investment Act - Press Release, 1967 (Box 1 (6-Communication), Folder 171)
  - Human needs vs. military spending, 1970 (Box 1 (6-Communication), Folder 172)
  - HUAC to Vote to Return Appropriation Back to Committee - Press Release, 1968 (Box 1 (6-Communication), Folder 173)
  - I.F. Stones Weekly - newsletter, 1967 (Box 1 (6-Communication), Folder 174)
  - Immigration Act Adversely Affects Irish Immigration - Press Release, 1967 (Box 1 (6-Communication), Folder 175)
  - Incentives for Antipollution Control, 1967 (Box 1 (6-Communication), Folder 176)
  - Indemnity Payments to Dairy Farmers - Press Release, 1967 (Box 1 (6-Communication), Folder 177)
  - Internal Revenue Code of 1954 - Press Release, 1967 (Box 1 (6-Communication), Folder 178)
  - Investigation of USA Crime - Press Release, 1967 (Box 1 (6-Communication), Folder 179)
  - Invitation to Housing Luncheon in Albany, 1967 (Box 1 (6-Communication), Folder 180)
  - Invitation to meet with Keith Hardy, 1967 (Box 1 (6-Communication), Folder 181)
  - Irish Immigrant amendment - Press Release, 1967 (Box 1 (6-Communication), Folder 182)
  - Israeli Independence Day, 1968 (Box 1 (6-Communication), Folder 183)
  - Jake Herzog for Congress, Undated (Box 1 (6-Communication), Folder 184)
  - Loyalty Day, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 1)
  - Lunch with Jerry Ford Program, 1968 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 2)
  - Luncheon - Reverand Krehel and Non-Profit Housing in Albany - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 3)
  - Mayor John V. Lindsey - Press Release, 1969; Undated (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 4)
  - A Measuring Stick Re: M.H. Yager, 1968 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 5)
  - Medicare Letter - Newsletter, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 6)
  - Meeting with Arbor Hill Group - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 7)
  - Memo, Undated (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 8)
  - Memo Calender, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 9)
  - Memorandum to answer letters accompanying the questionaries, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 10)
  - Memorandum for an effective congress report, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 11)
  - Letter on speech by J. Allen Overton JR, "The Credibility of Congress", 1967; Undated (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 12)
  - Letter to those who returned newsletter coupon, Undated (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 13)
  - Letter to volunteers for 1967 campaign, Undated (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 14)
  - Lowering Voting Age to 18 Years - Press Release, 1967; Undated (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 15)
  - Javits Anti-water Pollution Bill, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 16)
  - Joint Resolution Honoring Rush-Bagot Agreement, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 17)
  - Labor Day Statement - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 18)
  - Latham Colonie news - weeklies, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 19)
  - Launching the USS Schenectady, 1969 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 20)
  - Mid-decade census - Statement, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 21)
  - Mid East Resolution, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 22)
  - Military Aid to Greece Deplored, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 23)
  - 109th Military Airlift Group (letter from Colonel Poe) - Press Release, 1967; Undated (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 24)
  - Military Censorship on War Reporting - Press Release, 1968 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 25)
  - Mistake to Dismember OEO, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 26)
  - March for peace in Vietnam, Oneonta, New York, 1969 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 27)
  - National Council of Churches - Resolution on Congressional Standards, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 28)
  - National Defense Student Loan Monies Announcement - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 29)
  - National Education Association, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 30)
  - National Home Ownership Foundation Act - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 31)
  - National Institute for Crime Prevention and Control Bill, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 32)
  - National priorities hearing, 1970 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 33)
  - National Science Foundation, 1967; Undated (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 34)
  - Naval Academy Appointments - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 35)
  - The need to restore the 7 percent investment credit, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 36)
  - Negotiation NOW, Washington Luncheon - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 37)
  - New York Civil Liberties Union - newsletter, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 38)
  - New York State's proposed power sources, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 39)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 40)
  - Niskayuna Rotary Club, 1970 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 41)
  - North Atlantic Nations Convention, 1966-1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 42)
  - OEO - Neighborhood Service and Center Grant - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 43)
  - OEO press clips, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 44)
  - OEO responds to genuine needs, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 45)
  - OEO Supplemental Appropriation for Summer 1968 - Press Release (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 46)
  - "OEO's Work is Really Just Beginning" - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 47)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity - Radio scripts, Undated (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 48)
  - Oliver Wendell Holmes "The Great Dissenter", 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 49)
  - Opening Congressional Hearing on Federal Programs, Albany and Schementady - statement, 1968 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 50)
  - Operation Mainstream Grant to Cohoes - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 51)
  - Organized Credit Card Rocket - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 52)
  - On Pamphlets - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 53)
  - Percy housing bill recorded in Senate, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 54)
  - Plea Endorsed Button for Congress - Press Release, 1968 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 55)
  - Pomona Grange, 100 year anniversary, 1967; Undated (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 56)
  - Petition demanding open trial of auto smog conspiracy suit, 1969 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 57)
  - Petition for reconsideration of C.A.B. order, 1969 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 58)
  - Photo of Button (Duplicates), Undated (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 59)
  - Plea to House to create a select committee on standards and official conduct, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 60)
  - Poem, 1968 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 61)
  - Polish National Holiday, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 62)
  - Post Office, 1969 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 63)
  - Post Office and Civil Service Committee of The House, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 64)
  - Post Offices Annual Address Report - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 65)
  - Postal rates, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 66)
  - Postal Rates - statement, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 67)
  - PR highlights of the 90th Congress newsletter, 1968 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 68)
  - PR newsletter, 1968 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 69)
  - PR Record reprint "Responsible Representation", 1968 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 70)
  - PR samples, 1964-1966; Undated (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 71)
  - President's Commission on Selective Service - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 72)
  - President's Draft Message to Congress - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 73)
  - President's State of the Union Address - Press Release, 1969 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 74)
  - Presidents vetoes of both the education and HUD independent offices appropriations bills [roll call # 278-279], 1970 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 75)
  - Press Release, Appellate Court Rules Invalid 6% Air Fare Increase on Petition from DEB and 32 MC, 1970 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 76)
  - Press Release, Button announces AID Payments Received, 1968 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 77)
  - Press Release, Button Defense Contractors Conference, 1968 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 78)
  - Press Release, Button Remarks at Dr. King Memorial Service at Union College, Schenectady, 1968; Undated (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 79)
  - Press Release, Conservation Bill of Rights, 1968 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 80)
  - Press Release, Constantino Brumidi Ceremonies, 1968 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 81)
  - Press Release, The Death of Senator Kennedy, 1968; Undated (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 82)
  - Press Release, Employment Opportunities for Returning Vietnam Veterans, Con R 705, 1968; Undated (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 83)
  - Press Release, Hanoi Response to Peace Talks, 1968 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 84)
  - Press Release, H.E.W. Grant for Education Data Processing System, 1968 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 85)
  - Press Release, HUD Appropriation, FY 1969, DEB on Floor of House, 1968 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 86)
  - Press Release, Hudson River Project Hearing, 1968 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 87)
  - Press Release, Irish Immigration Bill goes to Judiciary Sub-Committee, 1968 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 88)
  - Press Release, Italian Earthquake Victims Bill, 1968 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 89)
  - Press Release List, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 90)
  - Press Release, Martin Luther King Statement, 1968 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 91)
  - Press Release, Memorial Day Speech (Albany Rural Cemetary), 1968 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 92)
  - Press Release, New York State Capitol Speech, 1969 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 93)
  - Press Release, Passage of 10 Percent Surcharge Tax, 1968 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 94)
  - Press Release, Sale of US Jet Fighters to Israel, 1968 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 95)
  - Press Release, Stabilization and Conservation Farm Service Program, Albany, Schenectady, 1968; Undated (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 96)
  - Press Release, Women Receive Full Social Security Benefits at 62 with 30 Years Coverage, 1968 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 97)
  - Priorities, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 98)
  - Probable close House and Senate races, 1968 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 99)
  - A program to provide free tickets to sporting events for underprivileged young people, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 100)
  - A proposal to prevent interstate smuggling ofcigarettes, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 101)
  - Protest of Port Visit to Capetown - Press Release, 1967; Undated (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 102)
  - Publication, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 103)
  - Pueblo Ship Seizure - Press Release, 1968 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 104)
  - Questionnaire Results - Press Release, 1968 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 105)
  - Radio and televation, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 106)
  - Radio and televation: "Report from Washington" WRGB - WEY, 1969 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 107)
  - Radio and TV WRGB news, 1969 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 108)
  - Radio Congressional comment, 1967-1968; Undated (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 109)
  - Radio interview on cigarette smuggling (Washington, next week), 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 110)
  - Radio Speech on Reserve Bill of Rights - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 111)
  - Radio Statement on House Rules - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 112)
  - Rat Bill - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 113)
  - Recommendation to Congressman Flood - Press Release, 1969 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 114)
  - Re-elect Dan Button - pins, bumper stickers, and handouts [NOTE: sharp rusty pins in Button face folder, exercise caution], 1968; Undated (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 115)
  - Re-Elect Dan Button - Speech Material and Press Releases, 1968; Undated (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 116)
  - Regionalism, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 117)
  - Registratio, Dates Memo, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 118)
  - Remarks to National Chamber of Commerce, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 119)
  - Representative Button Committee Assignment, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 120)
  - Republican Congressional Committee newsletter, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 121)
  - Republican Policy Committee - newsletter, 1967; Undated (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 122)
  - Republican on Agriculture Committee - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 123)
  - 27 Republicans Join Button's Committee on Urban Affairs - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 124)
  - RES to Eliminate HUAC - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 125)
  - Reserves, 1969 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 126)
  - Resolution Schenectady Branch, NAACP, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 127)
  - Response to Questionnaire - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 128)
  - Responsible representation (Bob Wilson), 1968; Undated (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 129)
  - Restoration of good government, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 130)
  - Ripon paper re: Vietnam, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 131)
  - Rockefeller Cigarette Committee - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 132)
  - Sale of 90 Acres of Scotia Naval Depot to SIDC - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 133)
  - Schedule for opening day of 90th Congress, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 134)
  - Schenectady Industrial development Council request to purchase Scotia Naval Depot, 1967; Undated (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 135)
  - Schenectady Student Wins Poster Contest - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 136)
  - Scholarships funds to School of Nursing at Albany Junior College, 1968 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 137)
  - Scotia Lions Club, 1968 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 138)
  - Script for July 4th, 1969; Undated (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 139)
  - Select Committee on Standards and Conduct - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 140)
  - Service academy appointments, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 141)
  - Service Academy Committee - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 142)
  - Social Security benefits to 29th district, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 143)
  - $5.5 million in Social Security benefits to residents of Albany and Schenectady, 1968 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 144)
  - Social Security legis - 90th club, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 145)
  - Special days of commemoration nationalities, 1967; 1969 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 146)
  - Speech at Carver Community Center, 1969 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 147)
  - Speech at Steinmetz Jr. High school, 1970 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 148)
  - Speech Material, 1965; 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 149)
  - Speech Material, Undated (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 150)
  - Speech material, radio texts on war, national properties and National Service Act of 1970, Undated (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 151)
  - Speech: Rotterdam Elks Club, 1970 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 152)
  - Speech to Local 234 UFPC, Schenectady, 1970 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 153)
  - Speech to Lodge 2353 - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 154)
  - Speech to Scotia Post 1001 American Legion, 1970 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 155)
  - Speeches and press releases on cigarette tax, includes commission report, 1964; 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 156)
  - State Cigarette Tax Bill - supplemental information, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 157)
  - Statement in Support of Elimination HUAC Resolution - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 158)
  - Statement in support of model cities, 1968 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 159)
  - Statement in support of National Endowment for the Humanities, 1968 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 160)
  - Statement on Arbor Hill Walk and Meeting - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 161)
  - Statement on campus ADA draft survey, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 162)
  - Statement on Counsular Treaty - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 163)
  - Statement on independent Maritime agency status, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 164)
  - Statement on NSF fellowship to Richard F. Ludeuna, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 165)
  - Statement on Presidential Civil Rights Legislation - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 166)
  - Statement on re-establishment of House Committee on standards and conduct, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 167)
  - Statement on resolution to eliminate HUAC, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 168)
  - Statement on the draft law extension, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 169)
  - Statement on lottery, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 170)
  - Statement on Middle East crisis, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 171)
  - Statement on Riots - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 172)
  - Statement on Vote to Bar Mr. Powell - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 173)
  - Statement on Watervliet Arsenal - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 174)
  - Statement on 18 year old vote, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 175)
  - Stockpile Disposed [9 bills passed non-record vote], Undated (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 176)
  - Student Intern Program - Press Release, 1967 (Box 2 (6-Communication), Folder 177)
  - Summer Interns - Press Release, 1967-1968 (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 1)
  - Support of mid-decade census bill, 1967 (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 2)
  - Support of resolution for employment of Vietnam veterans, 1968 (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 3)
  - Support 11089 - Increased Insurance for Fed Employees, 1967 (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 4)
  - Tariff action needed on paper industries machinery - Press Release, 1967 (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 5)
  - Tariff Rates - Press Release, 1967 (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 6)
  - Tax Credit for Education Expenses - Press Release, 1967 (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 7)
  - Tax Credit for Higher Education - Press Release, 1967 (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 8)
  - Teleprompter scripts, 1967 (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 9-10)
  - Testimonies and statements, 1970 (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 11-12)
  - The Coalition for Youth Action, 1968 (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 13)
  - "The Five Dollar Vote" - Press Release, 1967 (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 14)
  - "The Future of the American Federal System" - Speech of the Week, 1969 (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 15)
  - The Media Mix, 1967 (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 16)
  - The Ombudsmen Speak, 1967 (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 17)
  - "The Powell Case", 1967 (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 18)
  - The Ripon Forum - newsletters, 1965-1968 (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 19)
  - The State of the Union - a Republican Appraisal, 1968 (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 20)
  - The World Food Population Problem: an Overview, 1967 (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 21)
  - Transporting Man's Worldly Foods, 1967 (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 22)
  - Troy Police Benevolent and Protective Association Inc., 1968 (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 23)
  - TV Radio Enclosure Letter - Form Inserts, Undated (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 24)
  - UN resolution strengthening peace-keeping, 1967 (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 25)
  - "Unifying the Gordian Knot" - Insert, 1970 (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 26)
  - Updating ROTC, 1970; Undated (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 27)
  - Vietnam Speech (Albany Business College) - Press Release, 1967 (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 28)
  - Vietnam - Statement, Undated (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 29)
  - Vote on Rent Supplies and Model Cities - Press Release, 1967 (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 30)
  - Water pollution legislation, 1967 (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 31)
  - Watervliet Arsenal, 1968 (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 32)
  - Watervliet Arsenal Speech - Press Release, 1967 (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 33)
  - Weekly schedule for public relations and PR program for Congressional office, Undated (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 34)
  - White House press regulations, 1970 (Box 3 (6-Communication), Folder 35)
  - White House press regulations, 1970 (Box 4 (6-Communication), Folder 1)
  - Workshop Grand Approval - Press Release, 1967 (Box 4 (6-Communication), Folder 2)
  - World food needs, 1967 (Box 4 (6-Communication), Folder 3)
  - Union back button reprint from the Times-Union, 1968 (Box 4 (6-Communication), Folder 4)
  - United Church of Christ 4:10 Spot, 1968 (Box 4 (6-Communication), Folder 5)
  - U.S. Department of Agriculture hearings on revision of class I milk prices, 1967; Undated (Box 4 (6-Communication), Folder 6)
  - U.S. Oil Import Controls - Press Release, 1970 (Box 4 (6-Communication), Folder 7)
  - Veterans Affairs, 1968 (Box 4 (6-Communication), Folder 8)
  - Veterans Employment Resolution - Press Release, 1968 (Box 4 (6-Communication), Folder 9)
  - Veterans Hospital Alcoholism Bill - Press Release, 1967 (Box 4 (6-Communication), Folder 10)
  - Vietnam - The Clergyman's Dilemma, 1967 (Box 4 (6-Communication), Folder 11)
  - Vietnam, 1018th - Press Release, 1968 (Box 4 (6-Communication), Folder 12)
  - VITA cooperation between government and private sector, 1968 (Box 4 (6-Communication), Folder 13)
  - VITA volunteers, 1967 (Box 4 (6-Communication), Folder 14)
  - Voting at 18, statement and letter, 1970 (Box 4 (6-Communication), Folder 15)
  - Voting Irregulations in Albany County - Press Release, 1967; Undated (Box 4 (6-Communication), Folder 16)